strayeronline.net 2017-06-21

# Privacy Policy

Last Revised: July 20, 2016.

Strayer Education, Inc. and its subsidiaries including Strayer University ("Strayer") hold in high regard the privacy rights of visitors to our websites and mobile apps, including strayer.edu, strayeronline.net, strayereducation.com, strayeruniversity.edu, strayeruniversity.com, strayeredu.com, strayereducation.net, strayeruniversity.net, strayeruniversityonline.com, strayeruniversityonline.net, fcadealer.strayeruniversity.edu, and fca.strayeruniversity.edu, (the “Sites”). To demonstrate our commitment to user privacy, we provide the following information describing what information we collect from visitors to the Sites and how that information is used.

**By visiting the Sites or otherwise interacting with Strayer, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We suggest you review this Privacy Policy periodically, as it may be updated from time to time.**

  1. **Information Collected Automatically.** A variety of information is collected from visitors to the Sites. Some of this data is collected automatically via the use of cookies and other standard Web technology. Automatically-collected information might include: the operating system on your computer, the type of Web browser you are using, your IP address, and the links you followed to enter and leave our site. For more information on cookies and your choices, please review Advertising & Cookies, below.  
 
  2. **Information You Provide to Us.** Personally identifiable information may be collected on a voluntary basis, at the option of the user. For example, you may choose to provide your name, address or telephone number in the "Contact Us" section of our Sites or engage in financial transactions on the Sites.  
 
  3. **FERPA.** Personally identifiable information for enrolled students at Strayer University is protected by the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (“FERPA”) administered by the U.S. Department of Education. Additional information on FERPA is available here.  
 
  4. **Use of information.** Your information may be used to help us improve our Sites by enabling us to discover and address the needs of our Sites’ visitors. This includes making our Sites accessible to the variety of Web browsers and operating systems used to access our Sites.

Personal information collected through the Sites by means of your voluntary submission, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address and other contact information, is used for the purpose of responding to your requests for information about Strayer products and services or to contact you about future products and services. The Sites do not share personal information with third parties, apart from release of “directory information” as described in Strayer University’s FERPA policy or to certain authorized vendors bound by confidentiality agreements with Strayer who must utilize the information to perform necessary duties (such as credit card authorization, federal student aid processing and textbook ordering) or as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy. “Directory information” disclosures include verifying enrollment for employment or credit application purposes.

Subject to applicable laws, in the event that part or all of Strayer Education, Inc. or any of its subsidiaries are bought, sold or otherwise transferred, or is in the process of a potential transaction, personal information will likely be shared for evaluation purposes and included among the transferred business assets.

We may also disclose specific information when such disclosure appears necessary to comply with the law, a subpoena or other litigation process or to protect the interests or safety of visitors and customers, employees, students, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

  5. **Security of Information.** We use best efforts to protect the security of personal information collected through the Sites. Financial transactions submitted through the Sites are encrypted using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.  
 
  6. **Requesting Removal from Strayer Marketing Lists.** You may opt out of Strayer marketing solicitations at any time. Request removal from Strayer University’s marketing lists.  
 
  7. **Advertising & Cookies.** We partner with third party ad networks to either display advertising on our Sites or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partners use cookies and Web beacons to collect information about your activities on these and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you these types of targeted ads from Strayer, you may delete or disable cookies. Most browsers have a "Help" feature that will tell you how to do this. Please note, however, that disabling or blocking cookies may prevent some aspects of the Sites from working properly. For more information on interest-based advertising, and to review additional information on your opt-out options, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). In particular, we use Google Analytics to monitor activity on the Sites and make the Sites and our interactions with you more effective. To learn how Google Analytics collects and processes data, please visit: “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps” located [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners).  
 
  8. **Do Not Track.** Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At the present time, the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) has not yet established universal standards for recognizable DNT signals and therefore, the Sites and Strayer do not recognize DNT.  
 
  9. **Children’s Privacy.** The Sites do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13 without prior verifiable consent. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information online without parental consent, we will take all reasonable measures to delete the information from our databases and not use such information for any purpose, except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required or allowed by law.  
 
  10. **Your California Privacy Rights.** California residents are entitled to request and obtain from website operators once per calendar year information about personal information shared with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes, if applicable. The Sites do not currently share your personal information with third parties, except as described in this Privacy Policy. For any questions about sharing of your information and our privacy practices, please contact us as explained below.  
 
  11. **Limitation of Liability.** The Sites may contain links to third party websites. Links to these websites are provided as a convenience only and should not be interpreted as an endorsement of the linked site, its operator or contents. We encourage our visitors to review the privacy policies of each website they visit.  
 
  12. **Revisions to this Privacy Policy.** This Privacy Policy may be updated and revised from time to time, and we will post any changes to this policy. You agree that the information that we gather now will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may contact you with notices concerning our Privacy Policy, but you should check the Sites periodically to review any changes.  
 
  13. **For more information.** For further information about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
Strayer University Office of the General Counsel  
2303 Dulles Station Blvd.  
Mail Stop 6C  
Herndon, VA 20171  
E-mail:[ legal@strayer.edu](mailto:%20legal@strayer.edu?subject=Strayer%20Privacy%20Policy)

## 

You're ready for Strayer University
